[applause]
[cheering]
[music]
The one, the only
Max
[screaming]
[music]
[cheering]
Make some noise.
[music]
Thank you very much.
Wow. [music]
Wow. What an energy.
Wow.
[applause]
My [cheering] god. Where are my Persians
at?
[cheering]
[applause]
Where are my nonpersians at? [cheering]
Man, Toronto's representing, huh? This
is a great mixed audience. I love it.
Who's here?
Huh? [laughter]
What' you say?
Persian again.
Don't embarrass us in front of
everybody.
Again. Persians again.
I I want to scream louder.
I'm sorry. Give me another chance. I can
do better.
[applause]
Yes. Yes. Fantastic. This guy. Pink tie.
work.
You came from work.
You work for uh breast cancer awareness
or something.
What's up with the Pink Thai?
I'm curious. Where do you work for?
Where do you work?
Mercedes.
MercedesBenz.
So Persian this guy.
I work at the Mercedes-Benz downtown and
I wore this so you peek on me so I can
advertise. Uh,
good luck, man. You're gonna hold your
camera all night. If you keep holding
it, the security guard is going to come
here and shove it up your ass.
But judging from your pink tie, you're
going to like it.
[cheering]
[applause]
Guess who likes it more? They liked it
even more. They're like, "Yeah,
Toronto is wild, man.
Toronto is wild, baby. My god, where are
my Arabs in the house?"
[applause]
Where?
Sri Lankan. Sri Lankan. Since when Sri
Lankans turned Arab.
Europeans in the house. Make some noise.
Europeans. [cheering]
Nice. Nice. Nice. What country?
Netherlands. Nice. And you here on
vacation?
Just came for you.
Just came from me. From the Netherlands.
[laughter]
Are you [\h__\h] with me?
[applause]
Buddy, I owe you some gas money.
What are you saying? I I pay for the
hotel. Come stay at my place.
What do you do in Netherlands?
You're a genetic scientist.
Holy [\h__\h] That's pretty [\h__\h]
respectful, man. So, you genetically can
scientifically decide what the [\h__\h]
happening? Yeah.
I got to tell you,
I sincerely love what I do. And the most
special part of my show is when I get to
connect with you guys, get to know you
guys. I love it, man. It's the best
moment of my life. [applause]
I mean it.
I truly wish for everyone here Yeah. to
do something that they love. I hope you
guys love your jobs. But if you don't
love your job, it's still okay. Yeah.
Find something on the side that you
love, right? Have a passion in life. You
got to do something every day that makes
you happy. Even if your job is some
shitty MercedesBenz sales [\h__\h] they
make you wear a pink embarrassing tie.
Comedy is my passion and I love it. I've
loved it my entire life. And people
think it's easy to be a comedian. This
is not easy. People think I just go on
stage.
No. Like there's many different things
about my job is very difficult. Like
traveling is one of them. Traveling is
very very brutal. Going to city to city
to city. Yeah. Going to the airport,
dealing with the staff, dragging your
your luggage. It's really traveling is
so difficult. The other day I go to the
airport, I'm gate 18. I get there, they
have changed the gate. Where's the new
gate? 218.
I asked the lady, "Where is it?" She
goes, "5 days walk this way, sir."
Now I'm running like a crazy person in
the airport. You know how embarrassing
it is as an adult to run in the airport?
It's the worst feeling when you know
your gate is 20 minutes away, but you
got 5 minutes to get there.
That stress, the anxiety that kicks in,
if anybody knows the feeling, you run so
fast. You run faster than you ever run
in your life. You know what I'm TALKING
ABOUT? LIKE I'VE seen the most
unathletic people in the airport.
Run like no one's business. It's the
only time you run for your life, man.
When you know you're about to miss the
goddamn flight. You seen these people at
the airport? They're [\h__\h] running.
Like
[laughter]
I saw a 90-year-old with a walker. He
was just
at some point he took it behind his
back. He was like,
"You got to get to that plane, baby."
The other day I was so late. I'm
running. And when I say running, I was
running so fast. I run fast. I was
running like a freaking machine, man. I
was running so fast. All of a sudden, I
noticed somebody else is running right
next to me.
I start running even faster. I was going
so fast. This guy catches up with me. I
look at him. He goes, "Maxini."
[applause]
I was like, "Yes." He goes, "I love
you."
I said, "I love you, too, man." And
we're running. He goes, "Can I TAKE A
PICTURE?"
OH, BUDDY, I'M LATE. HE GOES, "It's
okay. I am late, too."
He took a picture. I look like this.
I was in the bathroom. Okay. I was
standing at a stall.
This dude walks into the bathroom,
comes right next to me.
[laughter]
[applause]
Maxamini
go. Yes. I love you.
As a straight man, you should never be
holding your dick telling another man,
"I love you."
CAN I TAKE A PICTURE?
WE'RE IN THE BATHROOM.
I said, "No, man. It's inappropriate."
"No, no, no. It's okay. It's going to be
funny.
It's very funny." I said, "No, man. It's
not right." He goes, "No, no, it's okay.
Please. You're the comedian. You tell me
how to make it funny."
I said, "You want it hilarious?" He
goes, "Yes, yes, hilarious." I said,
"Okay, let me piss on you. You take a
picture.
[applause]
I love you.
You mom going to take a piss on you,
too?
[applause]
I've been a fan since the 90s.
Oh, yeah.
This lady's been my fan since the '9s.
Yes. Yes.
Yes. I was not a comedian in the '9s.
No, I wasn't. You have a picture
of me in the '9s.
Uh, can you check the genetics on row
19,
CJ35? [cheering]
I think dementia is hitting. Yeah.
Tell her how old I am. Aren't you the
PhD scientist of the discovery of the
genetics?
Ask the doctor in the front. What? You
need to finger me to find out.
[cheering]
This guy, what kind of [\h__\h] doctor
are you? This is not a car mechanic shop
for you to oil change.
[laughter]
You're really my fan, huh?
A She's a sweetheart. I love you. Give
her a round of applause. [applause]
I'm I'm going to tell you something
tonight. You hear it from me. Age is
just a [\h__\h] ass number. You got to
feel good. You got to take care of
yourself. You got to live good. You
could be the oldest 30-year-old or the
youngest 70-year-old. Yeah. Live it like
strong, man. Every day counts. Laugh
every single day. Every single day.
[cheering and applause]
The other day I missed my flight. Yeah.
And I thought about this topic. I
thought I need to share this with my
audience. Yeah. So you guys never fall
into this trap. Okay. I miss my flight
and I'm letting you know when the door
of the plane is closed. Okay. by
aviation rules, they can't open it
again. So, don't beg those counter
people to open the door. I want my
friends to keep their pride and go home.
Yeah. Don't beg these people. These
counter people at the airport are some
of the meanest, most evil, twisted,
sick, psycho
zombies of all time. They're just
standing there like
You know how sick you got to be to take
that job? Just be so happy that
vulnerable people, they miss their
flight. They just stand there so excited
to tell them the door is closed.
They love doing this [\h__\h] They love it.
Don't beg them. Never give them the
pleasure. Keep your pride and walk away.
[laughter]
The other day I miss a flight. Okay. And
I told myself, I'm not even going to
look at this agent. All right. So, I get
there. I walk. I see her. Now, she's
bottled up. She couldn't wait. She was
so excited for this one person that
missing the fight to arrive and destroy
that person. She was just LIKE
standing there. I don't even give her
eye contact. I just walked by her. I
looked. I wanted to see if the door of
the plane is closed or not. I look, the
door is closed. I'm about to leave. I
can feel her energy. She's staring into
my soul.
And I'm looking at the door and I said,
"Let mess with her a little bit." Yeah.
Let me give her a taste of her own
medicine. I look at the door and I smile
so big as if I'm so happy the door is
closed. I went, "Ha ha."
And she got a little pissed because her
wires crossed.
Her brain, why is this guy happy that
the door is closed? I smile big and I
walk away. I'm leaving and as I'm
leaving, she can't help it. She screams,
"The door is closed."
I looked at her. I said, "Who gives a
shit?"
And I walked away. Oh my god, I said
that. She She died inside.
She has never in her entire career
experience somebody who doesn't care
about missing their flight. I walked
away. She couldn't help it. She screams
in the airport. Why?
Why?
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE A [\h__\h]
SHE had a meltdown.
I came back and I thought to myself, I'm
going to teach her a big lesson. I came
back and I said, "Ma'am, because I am
Iranian."
[applause]
And she was confused. She said, "What?"
I said, "We believe when we miss a
flight, it wasn't meant to be."
[applause]
That mean God has a plan for this plane
and he doesn't want me to be a part of
that plan.
From the bottom of my heart, good luck.
I walk away. She pissed herself.
She messages the pilot immediately. Oh
my god, a suspicious Iranian man
came to the counter and said, "God has a
plan for this plane."
And good luck. The pilot shot himself.
He calls the police, air marshal, TSA,
security. Everybody come. They cancel
the flight.
[applause]
I took the next flight. I arrived before
anybody else.
[cheering]
I saw an Iranian couple missed their
flight once and this is how I decided I
got to talk about this. I missed a
flight one day. As I'm leaving the
counter, I saw an Iranian couple running
to this counter. Yeah. And as they were
running, I was like, "Oh my god, I got
to watch this.
This is gold."
So like a little creep, I stood in the
corner
just to see what's [laughter] going to
happen.
The couple, they start running.
The husband gets to the counter. He
goes, "Oh, oh."
[laughter]
See, Iranians, we make certain sounds.
Only we understand what it means.
It has a distinct meaning. Yeah,
there sounds, no words needed, but we
know what it means.
It means something bad happened.
It means something horrible happened.
Okay? Do you want to learn how to do it?
If you want to do it properly, you have
to think and picture an owl
being fingered.
What does an owl sound like?
But when you finger the owl,
the pink dye guy loved it.
[applause]
The husband goes, "Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh."
The wife goes, "What happened?"
He goes, "We missed the fit."
She goes, "What are we going to do now?"
He goes, "Hurry." Her name was Huri.
Huri,
please do something.
Iranian men, they know they cannot do
[\h__\h] themselves anyways. [applause]
[cheering]
If anybody can do anything, it's the
women. [cheering]
That's right.
Confident Iranian woman looks at her
husband. She goes, "Don't worry about
it. I got you."
She walks up to the counter with so much
confidence.
Excuse me.
We have arrived. Open the door.
[applause]
The lady goes, "The door is closed."
Hoody goes, "Okay, okay. Okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay. Here comes
Persian negotiations at its best. Okay,
okay. Open the door a little bit. We go
inside.
Open the door a little bit. We go
Now, the white lady is going to be like,
"Oh my god, I didn't think a little bit
is not a problem. Oh my god, I thought
you wanted all the way open."
The lady goes, "The door is closed."
Dude, Julie realizes it's a bad
situation.
She goes, "Persian drama immediately."
Billy,
please
open the door.
Please,
open the door, please. The husband goes,
"Bye is not working."
Woody goes, "BILLY, [screaming]
we're at LAX airport in Los Angeles."
This lady goes bananas. [screaming]
Open the door. OPEN THE DOOR. I have
sexy.
PLEASE OPEN THE [laughter] DOOR. I'M
HAVING SURGERY. [screaming]
The husband goes, "Hurry, say it's your
birthday."
He's not even listening.
PLEASE, I HAVE SURGERY
on my birthday.
Open the door,
please,
dude. People are going, "What the hell?"
All of a sudden, Hoody realizes it's not
working. She changes tactic.
Excuse me,
are you married?
The most thing you can do. The lady,
she's an evil [\h__\h] Nobody marries her.
She goes, "No, I'm single." She goes, "I
p for you.
I will pray for you. I will pray for
you. As if she's Jesus Christ.
I pray. Beautiful man come into your
life. I will pray. As she's praying, the
plane takes off.
Hoodie and the husband realize game
over. [laughter]
Hoodie snaps.
I P IT [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] YOU. [\h__\h] you.
[\h__\h] you.
The husband goes, "Hurry, relax."
She turns to the husband. "FUCK YOU,
TOO.
[\h__\h] you."
[applause]
The husband goes, "You haven't [\h__\h] me
for 40 years.
[applause]
You never [\h__\h] me.
Here it is. [\h__\h] me.
[applause]
[screaming]
[laughter]
You go to standby. You guys know what
happens at standby. Yeah. When you miss
your flight, you go to the next flight
that's going to the same destination.
Yeah. But you have to wait for them to
get all the passengers on the plane
first once everybody's on board. If
there's any room on the plane, they call
your name. Hurry. Every 10 minutes goes
to the counter. [laughter]
Excuse me. Did you call Hoody?
They're like, "Ma'am, please wait."
Okay, you have to wait till the end.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Hoodie comes back and
the husband, they make a picnic.
She pulls out 50 napkins she stole from
McDonald's.
She opens it up. Pistachio, cashew,
sunflower seeds, cucumber, tomatoes,
eggplant.
She starts making sandwiches.
Every 5 minutes, Huri will go to the
counter. Excuse me, did you call Huri?
They're like, ma'am, please go sit down.
At the very end, we'll call you. Okay,
okay, okay. 5 minutes later, she would
take some pistachios. Excuse me. Do you
like pistachio?
Did you call huri?
Hi, please have a seat. Okay. O
10 times she go. Did you call huri?
Finally at the very end there's only one
seat available.
They call my name.
[applause]
Who gets electrocuted?
I grab my bag. I'm going to the plane.
Hoodie steps up. Excuse me, Maxami.
I turn around. Hi, Hoodi.
Oh, how do you know my name?
I said, to be honest with you, the whole
airport knows your name.
Really? I said, yes. Who? He goes, "You
know, you're an honorable Iranian artist
and I am an older Iranian woman. How
could you walk in front of me and not
offer me your seat?"
Immediately, I pulled out my boarding
pass. And I gave it to her. I said, "Go
ahead, Hoodie. You can have a seat."
Hoody couldn't believe it. She's like,
"Oh my god,
thank you. I can't believe you gave it
to me." I said, "Of course, Hoodi. Why
would I not give it to you? You have
surgery
on your birthday.
She goes, "Oh, I was lying."
I said, "It's okay. Go ahead." She goes,
"No, I cannot go. We need two seats, me
and my husband. Here, you go." She gives
me the boarding pass and I go, "Hoodie,
what are you doing?
You knew there's only one seat. She
goes, "I know.
I just wanted to come up and talk to you
because I'm a big fan.
I remember you from the '9s."
[applause]
I said, "Hoody, I wasn't a comedian in
the '9s." She goes, "Yes, you were a
comedian.
I have a picture with you.
She goes, "Can I ask you a favor?" I
said, "What is it?" She goes, "Can you
come in the bathroom and take a picture
with me?
I wanted to be very funny." [laughter]
My god. I took the boarding pass. I
walked on the plane. And I was really
happy. I'm like, "Oh my god, I'm going
to make it to my destination." You know
the feeling sometimes? you start your
day. It's sort of shitty. Yeah, it
doesn't go your way, but it's working
out. I That's how I felt. I'm like, man,
I'm on the plane now. This is great. I
look at my boarding pass. My seat 28B. I
walk up to my seat.
I couldn't believe this [\h__\h] 28B was
missing.
I look I look at the boarding pass.
There's no seat.
My seat happened to be between two of
the biggest humans on planet Earth.
[laughter]
These two guys were so big my seat in
the middle disappeared.
I couldn't believe it. I looked I looked
at the flight attendant. Excuse me. 28B
is missing. She knew what's happening.
She goes, "Sir, your seat is right
there." And then she ran away.
I'm like, "What?" I look at the guys. I
go, "Sorry, guys. That's my seat." The
guys looked at each other. "What seat?"
I said, "The crack right there."
[applause]
They look between their biceps together
unison. They're like, "We're going to
make it happen."
I said, "Thank you so much." The guy
said, "Can you turn around?"
I trusted him. I turned around. He
grabbed the back of my pants and he
started pulling. Now the guy is pulling.
I'm right at the crack. Okay. The other
guy is pushing himself to the window.
He's just pancake to the window. This
guy is pulling my pants. I'm right
between them, right? And all of a SUDDEN
HE GOES, "PUSH, PUSH."
I'm like, "Okay, I'm pushing loud." He
goes, "Push, [screaming] push." I'm
like, "I'm pushing." PUSH. YOU'LL BECOME
AERODYNAMIC. I'm like, "Okay, I BECOME
AERODYNAMIC." PUSH. AND THEY GOT
PUSHING.
PAUSE. PUSHING.
THEN HE GOES, "Bend over. Excuse me.
Don't worry. I'm a professional." I'm
like, "Okay."
Aerodynamic. I bend over. HE GOES,
"PUSH." I'M PUSHING NOW. THE WHOLE PLANE
GOES PUSH, PUSH.
It was like giving birth, but the other
way around.
I was trying to go inside the hole.
PUSH, PUSH. [screaming]
I WENT RIGHT BETWEEN THE CRACK. It was
amazing. I WAS GOING INSIDE. PUSH. AND
THEN I GOT STUCK. EVERYONE'S LIKE,
"PUSH, PUSH, PUSH." I WAS TURNING RED.
I'M PUSHING.
All of a sudden, THE GUY GOES, "WAIT, I
HAVE VASELINE."
[applause]
I go, "How do you have Vaseline?" He
goes, "I work for Mercedes-Benz
downtown."
[applause]
He put ON SOME VASELINE. PUSH.
[screaming] EVERYONE'S PUSH. I'M
PUSHING. BOOM. I FELL INSIDE.
Oh my god. I fell inside the hole. I've
never felt this comfortable in my life
before.
The best feeling in the world. This was
the best hole I've ever experienced.
It was so gushy mushy.
Honestly, I've never felt this good
before. I'm inside. I'm between these
two guys in this little hole. Oh my god.
You know, you got to take those donut
little pillows for the plane. I needed
nothing.
Every crevice of my body was filled.
I'm sitting there like a baby. I'm like,
"Oh my god."
I felt like I was between two
tempropedic pillows.
So good, man. Plane takes off. I fall
asleep. I never fall asleep on the
plane. I immediately fell asleep like a
baby. Like
I sleep for 4 hours. 4 hours later, I
wake up. I open my left eye.
Everything else was covered.
[laughter]
Looking around, I saw the flight
attendant. The flight attendant saw me.
She freaked out. She's like, "Oh my
god."
She saw a hole and a eyeball just
sticking out.
Are you okay?
I blinked twice for yes.
She goes, "Sir, would you like something
to drink?" I said, "No, thank you.
I've already been breastfed."
Now, if this plane would have crashed, I
would have been the only survivor.
What just happened?
I like this audience. This is a good
show. Look at this two couple. So
stylish. I just noticed. I'm sorry. I
didn't recognize sooner. My god, you
couldn't wait for me to pick on you.
Look at your glasses.
Half white, half black.
Your girlfriend bright pink.
My god. Oh, married. I'm sorry.
Mash made in heaven. You saw each other.
Oh my god. Oh my god. What's your name,
buddy?
Hussein.
Hussein. And
you guys uh you're into fashion.
You teach fashion.
No. And this is the [\h__\h] result.
[applause]
She ordered the most ridiculous glasses.
Can I borrow those glasses, please?
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm going to teach
you how to look more stylish.
[applause]
Honey, I love you. How do I look?
You look fly, baby. Oh my god. Thank you
very much.
Give it up for Hussein, everybody.
Love you, man. [applause]
As soon as the show's over, throw him
away.
What is an evil laugh?
She has the laugh of those airline
counter ladies.
[laughter]
My family, my entire family, they're
crazy.
So when I see a crazy, I connect. Yeah.
And I feel good. Now, I'm telling you,
my whole family is crazy. Every family
at least has one crazy person, right? At
least one. You know what I'm talking
about? We all have that one crazy person
in our family. And when she calls, when
he calls, we're all like, "Oh shit." The
crazy person shows up to Thanksgiving.
Oh [\h__\h] If you're sitting here like,
"Oh, my family is perfect." If you think
there's no crazy person in your family,
you're the one.
One of my uncles, he is such an intense,
nerve-wracking stress freak. Yeah. He
tells me, "Max, I want to fly with you
from LA to DC." I said, "Sure." Okay. I
pick him up. He gets into the car. I've
never seen him this nervous ever before.
He's shaking. He's worried. He's got
anxiety. I go, "Uncle, you okay?" He
goes, "No, no, no. Yes, yes, yes. No,
no, yes. No, no, not yes. No, no, no.
I'm not okay." I go, "What's going on?"
He goes, "We're going to the airport.
Every time I go to the airport, they
randomly select me.
You get it?" I'm like, "Yes." He goes,
"No, you don't get it. But it's SO
RANDOM IF IT'S EVERY TIME.
I am not terrorist."
I go, "I know you're not terrorist."
Uncle, relax. He goes, "No. Do you think
I'm terrorist? I've been shaving since
7:00 last night.
It's already growing back.
I think the metal detector detects how
much body hair you have.
He has his own philosophies.
He's super nervous. I go, I'm just going
to relax. He's like, "No, no, no, no.
You don't understand. I am very
worried." Okay, we get there, they pick
me in front of everybody, they select
me. People, my friends think I am
terrorist. I go, "Okay, just just calm
down." And then he starts talking to
himself. This is what older Iranian men
do. He sits there. He starts literally
just sitting right next to me in the
car.
They're singing to me.
I go, "Uncle, you okay?" BUT THEY DON'T
KNOW WHO I AM.
I go, "WHO ARE YOU? I AM A KID."
I go, "Okay, relax." I'd never seen them
this nervous. We get to the airport.
We're standing in line.
Man, he literally is shaking.
We're standing in security line. He is
so nervous.
He makes me nervous.
He made me so nervous. Now I'm shaking.
We're two Middle Easterns just shaking,
walking so suspiciously in the lineup.
Dude, we get to the front. The officer,
he's just very chill. And my uncle is so
tense. He goes, "Sir, can you step up?"
Everything he says, MY UNCLE REPEATS, "I
STEP UP.
THE GUY GOES, "YES, SIR. Can I have your
ID?" He goes, "ID."
The officer takes the ID, looks at the
ID, looks at my uncle and goes, "You've
been selected for a random search, sir."
My uncle gets so mad. And when he gets
angry, you can't understand what he's
saying.
The officer looks at me, goes, "Sir, I
don't understand what he's saying. are
you together? I said, "No, I have no
idea who he is."
YOU LOOK I CHANGE YOUR DIAPER. I CHANGE
YOUR DIAPER. I SAID, "SIR, I'm a grown
ass man. I don't wear diaper."
They take him to the side. Oh. Oh.
Oh. Oh.
They give him some Mercedes-Benz
dealership.
I haven't spoken to that uncle in 10
years.
Man, after I saw that incident, I
thought to myself, you know what? Never
let anybody make you feel that
uncomfortable. Yeah. You make them
uncomfortable.
Yeah.
Why would you let someone stress you out
so much like that? Now, every time I go
to the airport, I take a revenge
on behalf of my uncle. [laughter]
I go stand in the security line and
pretend I can't wait to be selected. I
just stand there so happy. Hi, I
volunteer. Like, sir, get back in line.
Okay. I go a little bit more. Hello, I
would love the body search.
And you get to the front and immediately
go, "Sir, you're selected for a random
chick." I'm like, "Yes,
yes." And they take me to the side and
they ask me, they always ask you, "Sir,
would you like a private screening or a
public screening?"
Public.
Can you spread your legs? Yes.
Officer search me
and as soon as they touch me, I START
MOANING. OH.
YES, [screaming]
OFFICER.
I'm hiding. Oh, yes, officer. A little
higher. You can find my genetics.
Yes.
[cheering and applause]
They usually freak out. They're like,
"Get the [\h__\h] out of here. Go back to
Netherlands." Thank you.
But but I'm just saying like in life you
got to just really entertain yourself.
Isn't that like I'm telling you if you
don't you get depressed. Yeah. You got
to you got to try. You got to get out of
the house. You got to do [\h__\h] It takes
effort. Otherwise you regret. Yeah. You
want to do the [\h__\h] you're scared of.
Personally, I want to share with you one
of the scariest, most exciting
experience in my life. And to be honest
with you, I didn't really choose to face
my fear. In this case, the fear faced
me. Okay. Who here has done skydiving
before? [cheering] Yes. Oh wow. Where
did you jump?
Afghanistan. Ah, I see. You were
escaping Afghanistan.
That's completely different. Hhabibi,
we're talking about recreational stuff.
Yeah. Not escaping Afghanistan. Were you
the guy we're hanging on the plane? Good
to see you, man. You made it. White
people laugh. It's okay.
This is all okay. It's crowd. We're
having fun. He knows we're good. Okay.
So, I'm in Dubai. I'm doing a radio
interview and on air the girl that was
interviewing me, she loved skydiving and
she couldn't stop talking about it. She
goes, "Oh my god, it's the best thing in
the world. Every time I jump out of the
plane, adrenaline and hits my body,
comes out of my ears and my nipples get
hard. It's amazing." And then she keeps
telling me, "Do you like it? what would
you do? How would you jump? And I was
trying to be fun on the air. I was like,
I don't know. I'll backflip and belly
dance all the way down. And she's like,
"Oh my god, that's so amazing." So, we
were laughing, having a good
conversation. The interview ends. The
manager of the radio station walks in
and she goes, "Oh my god, Max, I love
the interview. This was so great. We
have a surprise for you." [laughter] I
go, "Huh?"
He goes, "We called Dubai Skydiving
and we we squeezed you in. They're
always booked, but they allowed us to
take you right now." I was like, "All
of a sudden, the whole station starts
screaming, celebrating." Yes. Yes. THE
LADY'S LIKE, "AH."
I WAS LIKE, "OKAY." NOW, I'm scared of
heights.
I didn't know what to say. I was like,
"Okay, it was already a done deal. We
get in the car. We go to the place. Not
the whole time inside. I'm freaked out.
We get there. They gave me an Arab
instructor. I'm standing there. The guy
sits between my legs. He he I put on the
parachute and he's pulling the the the
straps. Okay. If you've never done this
here, I tell you exactly what goes
through your mind. I'm standing there
and all I can think is what if this
parachute doesn't open?
I couldn't stop thinking about this
[\h__\h] My brain was constantly just
twirling the same thought over and over.
What if this doesn't open? I fall out of
the plane. And I started seeing myself.
The parachute didn't open. Now I'm I'm
seeing it happen in front of me as I'm
standing there. I fell out of the plane.
I exploded.
I exploded. My legs went one way. My
arms. And as I was watching, I saw my
dick.
flying in the air. It's like, "What the
fuck?"
And I got concerned. What's going to
happen to my dick? [laughter]
I was watching. ALL OF A SUDDEN, an
eagle flew by.
[screaming]
THE EAGLE GRABBED MY dick
and flew to the highest mountain
and fed the baby eagles.
Have you seen it on Discovery Channel
how hungry these babies are? Like
[screaming]
it was the most delicious meat they've
ever had in their life.
All of a sudden, my instructor is
pulling so hard on the strap. I come
back to reality and he goes, "It's
tight. It's very good. Very tight. Very
good. Very tight. Very good. Tight. Very
good. Very good. Very tight. Very good.
Very tight. Very good. Very good. Very
tight." I go, "What are you doing?" Go.
It's very tight. It's very good. I go,
"I know. He was such a pervert.
my luck. I got an Arab pervert
instructor.
He's got the googlying eyes. It's very
tight. Very good. Very tight. Very good.
Very good. Very tight. I go, "Habibi,
it's tight. It's very good. Let it go."
He goes, "Okay, follow me." I follow the
guy. We go into the small plane. We sit
on the plane now. It's a small plane.
All these people are so excited. Plane
takes off. The higher the plane goes,
more excited my instructor gets.
All of a sudden, we get to the right
altitude. The pilot guy gets on the
walkie thing and he speaks in Arabic
when we're when we're in UAE and he
goes,
"My Arabic is fantastic."
I I explained to you what he said. He
said, "Now we have arrived to the right
altitude.
Uh, if you make it down there, there's
going to be free hummus and schwarma."
They all of a sudden open the door of
the plane. Air hits [snorts] in. What a
weird feeling. Air comes in.
That air comes in, dude. It's the
scariest thing you can experience.
People jump out of the plane and they
disappear.
Like, it's weird. They jump and go,
"What?" ALL OF A SUDDEN, MY INSTRUCTOR
GOES, "HABIBI, HABIBI, HABIBI." I go,
"What?" He goes, "Sit on my lap."
Now, I didn't know about this part. I
thought this guy is a pervert.
He's trying to get me like jump on his
lap, you know, because I'm nervous all
of a sudden. I don't know what's
happening, you know? I was like, "Hell
no. He's like, "Habib yala. Habibi
yalah." I said, "No, sir. I'm not going
to sit on your lap." All of a sudden,
this guy grabbed me, lifts me, and puts
me on his lap.
Dude, I'm a grown ass man
sitting on another man's lap. He has a
hook on his jacket, and he hooked in on
the back of mine. So, I'm stuck to him
like this.
His mustache is tickling my neck.
I stop breathing like
I don't want to make one inch move just
in case this guy gets excited
and I experience some Arabic surprise.
All of a sudden he goes, "Habib, let's
go." I get up. I'm like, "Okay, okay,
okay, okay." The door of the plane is
open. Oh my god. This is the scariest
time. You're standing there at the door
of the plane and the guy goes, "Jump."
I look down.
[\h__\h]
I saw the whole galaxy.
MARS, PLUTO,
EARTH. They were all like [\h__\h]
twirling around each other having a
great time.
THIS GUY LIKE JUMPED in that moment. I
was like, "What am I doing?" If 1% this
parachute doesn't open,
I'm gonna die.
Are you crazy, Max? You have a good
life.
Don't do this. In that moment, I decided
I'm not going to jump. Now, THE
INSTRUCTOR KEEPS YELLING, "JUMP, GO.
JUMP." I said, "No."
He goes, "Habibi, go." I said, "Habibi,
no."
HE GOES, "HABIB, YALL." I SAID, "NO." He
goes, "Go." I said, "Sir, no means no."
He goes, "Let's go."
[applause]
I fell out of the plane holding my
[\h__\h]
[screaming]
[applause]
DUDE IS SCREAMING, "OPEN YOUR LEGS. OPEN
YOUR LEGS. YOU HAVE TO COME DOWN LIKE
THIS." I WAS LIKE, "HELL [screaming]
NO."
HE GOES, "HABIBI, OPEN YOUR LEGS." I GOT
NO WAY.
HE GOES, "HABIB, WE'RE GOING TO DIE." I
SAID, "I WILL DIE. A VIRGIN, ASSHOLE."
HE'S LIKE, "HABIBI."
DUDE, HE WAS FREAKING OUT. EVERYBODY
ELSE were like this, coming down slow.
Him and I were coming down so fast.
We're like,
we're coming down, [screaming]
dude. We hit the ground. We hit the
ground so hard. And he's my instructor.
He's underneath. He hits the ground
first. Boom. He hits. His dick breaks.
HIS ARABIC DICK FLIES IN THE AIR. I was
like, "OH MY GOD, IT HAPPENED. HIS
Arabic dick was going in the air." Out
of nowhere, an eagle flew by.
Grabs the Arabic dick. But he but the
but the eagle was struggling with the
dick.
It was too heavy.
Second eagle flew by.
TWO EAGLES TOOK THE ARABIC DICK,
flew to the highest mountain AND FED ALL
THE EAGLE babies in the world.
[applause]
They asked me, "Sir, how was your
experience?" I said, "What part? the
jump or the penetration.
Thank you very much.
[music]
Thank you. Thank you very [cheering]
much. [music]
Thank you. [music]
[music]
I a a